Hello friends, see you all on the next channel.
Welcome to today's video.
We are going to discuss the results of ICC Lombard.
ICC Lombard has also announced a dividend,
but we are going to see its face value. The
figure is in lakh rupees, so we will
convert it into crores, so a
total of 525 crores, which was
4362 crores in the last quarter.
If we talk about expenses, out of 3976
crores, there were
expenses of four zeros and five crores in the same
quarter of last year, there were expenses of 3626 crores.
If we look at it on a quarter-on-quarter basis, there is an
expense loss of 2.6%, which is a good
thing. And if we
look at it on a quarter-on-quarter basis, then expenses are almost 10%
bigger.
If we talk about profit, the
net profit is
436 crores,
which was a net profit of 352 crores in the last quarter
and
312 crores
bigger in the same quarter of last year, which is a very good growth for the company.  If
you have seen
this video so closely, then if
you like the information in this video, then do
not forget to like the video and subscribe to the channel. Jai
Hind.